{
    "subject": "Isabel_Coixet",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "My_Life_Without_Me",
    "human_readable": "Isabel Coixet directed the film My Life Without Me.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8897370100021362,
            "question": "Who directed the film My Life Without Me?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8458679914474487,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Isabel Coixet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8390499949455261,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Isabel Coixet."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6657224893569946,
            "question": "Has Isabel Coixet directed any other notable films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5632593631744385,
            "question": "Who are some of the actors in My Life Without Me?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5510683059692383,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the plot of My Life Without Me?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4382164776325226,
            "question": "What year was My Life Without Me released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4358797073364258,
            "question": "What genre is My Life Without Me likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41686129570007324,
            "question": "Are there any themes explored in My Life Without Me?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3754197955131531,
            "question": "What awards or recognition has My Life Without Me received?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Isabel Coixet directed the film My Life Without Me.",
            "html": "yago_9117_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any themes explored in My Life Without Me?",
            "html": "yago_9117_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is My Life Without Me likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_9117_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was My Life Without Me released?",
            "html": "yago_9117_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9117_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9117_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9117_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9117_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9117_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9117_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9117_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9117_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9117_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9117_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information about the film \"My Life Without Me,\" which was indeed directed by Isabel Coixet. Therefore, the statement that Isabel Coixet directed the film \"My Life Without Me\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}